<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Taha Draidia</title>
    <link>https://tahadraidia.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Taha Draidia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tahadraidia.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s build a Python module in C</title>
      <link>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/python-c-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/python-c-module/</guid>
      <description>Background Python is one of the most used programming language nowadays specially due its popularity in data science, deep and machine learning fields; Truth to be told, under the hood there is C and/or C++ code running.
Let&amp;rsquo;s take for example some popular python libraries used in math and machine learn to illustrate that point:
 Numpy (33.2% of the code is written in C) TensorFlow (61% of the code is written in C++) PyTorch (53% of the code in written in C++ and 4% in C)  The raison that these libraries are build in C and/or C++ is for performance issues mainly, also it is important to note that Python is written in C, hence it provides a C API to extend the language by creating new modules at lower-level possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michał Bentkowski XSS Challenge</title>
      <link>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/micha%C5%82-bentkowski-xss-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/micha%C5%82-bentkowski-xss-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Back in April, Michał Bentkowski posted an XSS challenge on twitter. So I decided to give this a try and here is my write-up about it.
The first thing that I noticed when I visited the page is that the challenge was served via GitHub Pages. From there, I knew that CSP did not apply to the challenge.
The challenge rules were as follows:
Please enter some HTML. It gets sanitized and inserted to a &amp;lt;div&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivering more than just presents: An Xmas story of self-XSS on Amazon.com</title>
      <link>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/xmas-amazon-self-xss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/xmas-amazon-self-xss/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since my last blog post, as I was preparing for my OSCP. Well, I&amp;rsquo;m glad to inform you all that I&amp;rsquo;m now an Offensive Security Certified Professional.
In this post, I will walk you through how, in less than five minutes, I found a self-XSS bug on the main Amazon.com website.
It was Chrismas time and a colleague of mine had introduced me to Amazon Prime Video, so I decided to take a look at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OverTheWire&amp;#58; Natas 0-10</title>
      <link>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/on-the-wire-natas-0-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/on-the-wire-natas-0-10/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for OSCP, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working through OverTheWire - natas and here is my walktrough for levels 0-10. Natas is a series of insecure webapps, which aim to teach the basics of web security.
The security topics covered in these levels include:
 Editing HTTP headers Editing cookies File inclusion vulnerabilities Bruteforce techniques Command injections  Natas 0 It says that we can find the password for the next level on the page, yet we don&amp;rsquo;t see it, do we ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Robot Vulnhub Challenge Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/mr-robot-boot2root-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/mr-robot-boot2root-challenge/</guid>
      <description>I had some extra time this weekend so I decided to play Mr Robot hacking challenge. I heard a lot about that challenge but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to hack it. Now was the time. I downloaded the virtual machine image from vulnhub, fired up virtulbox, started kali linux vm.
Enumeration time, I always start with port scanning to see what services are running but to do so I need to find the machine&amp;rsquo;s IP first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bypass Content Security Policy framing restriction rule - OLX</title>
      <link>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/bypass-csp-framing-restriction-rule-olx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/bypass-csp-framing-restriction-rule-olx/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since my last post. Today I decided to share with you a bug I found on a public bug bounty program on HackerOne. You can find the original report here.
This post is about a misconfiguration in CSP rule that leaves the website vulnerable to UI redressing aka clickjacking. This attack is widly used by scammer and spammers to trick users.
After some recon on olx.co.za and olx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflective XSS via angularJS template injection - Hostinger</title>
      <link>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/xss-via-angularjs-template-injection_hostinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/xss-via-angularjs-template-injection_hostinger/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a write-up of an AngularJS Template Injection I found in the main domain of Hostinger. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s client-side template injection I invite you to take a look at those links [1][2]. Please note that this is my first write-up, I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy it.
It all started when @berkanexo was telling me that he got listed on Hostinger Wall Of Fame so I decided to take a look at their website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Blog ! My goals for 2018</title>
      <link>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/git-init-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tahadraidia.com/posts/git-init-blog/</guid>
      <description>Hello world, welcome to my little paradise, I&amp;rsquo;m Taha Ibrahim DRAIDIA, I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer interested in application security, binary exploitation, exploit developement, ethical hacking and bug bounties. I never wrote a blog before, this my first time, I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll like my writings. Below are the reasons why I decided to start writing a blog:
 I used to take notes on text files, they got messy I would like to share what I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt along my journey in computers I would like to increase my writing skills I would like to get feed back about my code, researchs and methodologies I would like to feel more connected with people who share the same interests  Here is a list of topics which I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing about:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
